<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="console-application">
  <id>org.kde.kdialog</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>KDialog</name>
  <name xml:lang="be">KDialog</name>
  <name xml:lang="bg">KDialog</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">KDialog</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">KDialog</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">KDialog</name>
  <name xml:lang="da">KDialog</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">KDialog</name>
  <name xml:lang="el">KDialog</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">KDialog</name>
  <name xml:lang="eo">KDialog</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">KDialog</name>
  <name xml:lang="et">KDialog</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">KDialog</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">KDialog</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">KDialog</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">KDialog</name>
  <name xml:lang="hi">के-डायलॉग</name>
  <name xml:lang="hu">KDialog</name>
  <name xml:lang="ia">KDialog</name>
  <name xml:lang="id">KDialog</name>
  <name xml:lang="is">KDialog</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">KDialog</name>
  <name xml:lang="ka">KDialog</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">KDialog</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">KDialog</name>
  <name xml:lang="nn">KDialog</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">KDialog</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">KDialog</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">KDialog</name>
  <name xml:lang="ro">KDialog</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">KDialog</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">KDialog</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">KDialog</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Kdialog</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">KDialog</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">KDialog</name>
  <name xml:lang="vi">KDialog</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxKDialogxx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-CN">KDialog</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-TW">KDialog</name>
  <summary>Display dialog boxes from shell scripts</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="be">Паказваць дыялогавыя вокны для скрыптоў праграмнай абалонкі</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="bg">Показване на диалогови прозорци от скриптове на обвивката</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Mostra quadres de diàleg des de scripts de l'intèrpret d'ordres</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Mostra diàlegs des de scripts de l'intèrpret d'ordres</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Anzeige von Dialogen aus Shell-Skripten</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="el">Εμφανίζει πλαίσια διαλόγου από σενάρια φλοιού</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">Display dialogue boxes from shell scripts</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eo">Montri dialogskatolojn el ŝelskriptoj</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Mostrar cuadros de diálogo desde los scripts del intérprete de órdenes</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="et">Shelliskriptidega dialoogikastide näitamine</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">Bistaratu elkarrizketa-koadroak «shell script»etatik</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Näytä komentotulkkiskriptistä kyselyikkunoita</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Affiche des boîtes de dialogue depuis un script shell</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Mostrar cadros de diálogo a partir de scripts de intérprete de ordes</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hi">शेल स्क्रिप्टों से संवाद बक्से प्रदर्शित करें</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hu">Párbeszédablakok megjelenítése parancsfájlokból</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ia">Monstra quadratos de dialogo ex scripts de shell</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="id">Displai kotak dialog dari skrip shell</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="is">Birtir samskiptaglugga frá skeljaskriftum</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Visualizza finestre di dialogo da script di shell</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ka">სკრიპტებიდან ფანჯრების ჩვენება</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">셸 스크립트에서 대화 상자 표시</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Dialoogvensters uit shell-scripts</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nn">Vis dialogvindauge frå kommandolinjeskript</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Wyświetla okna dialogowe ze skryptów powłoki</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Mostra janelas a partir de programas</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Mostra caixas de diálogo a partir scripts do shell</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ro">Afișează casete de dialog din scripturi de consolă</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ru">KDialog служит для показа диалоговых окон из сценариев оболочки</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Zobraziť dialógové okná zo shellových príkazov</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Prikažite pogovorna okna iz shell skripta</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Visa dialogrutor från skalskript</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">Kabuk betiklerinden iletişim kutuları görüntüler</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Відкриття діалогових вікон з скриптів командної оболонки</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="vi">Hiển thị các hộp thoại từ các kịch bản hệ vỏ</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxDisplay dialog boxes from shell scriptsxx</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-CN">从 Shell 脚本中显示对话框</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-TW">在 Shell 指令稿顯示對話框</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      kdialog allows you to display dialog boxes from shell scripts.
      The syntax is very much inspired from the "dialog" command
      (which shows text mode dialogs).
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="be">kdialog дазваляе вам паказваць дыялогавыя вокны са скрыптоў абалонкі. Сінтаксіс шмат у чым узяты з загаду "dialog" (якая паказвае дыялогі тэкставага рэжыму).</p>
    <p xml:lang="bg">kdialog ви позволява да показвате диалогови прозорци от шел скриптове. Синтаксисът е вдъхновен от командата "dialog" (която показва диалог  в текстов режим).</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El KDialog permet mostrar quadres de diàleg des de scripts de l'intèrpret d'ordres. La sintaxi està molt inspirada en l'ordre «dialog» (la qual mostra diàlegs en mode text).</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">KDialog permet mostrar diàlegs des de scripts de l'intèrpret d'ordres. La sintaxi està molt inspirada en l'ordre «dialog» (la qual mostra diàlegs en mode text).</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Mit KDialog können grafische Dialoge aus Shell-Skripten aufgerufen werden. Die Syntax ist vom Befehl „dialog“ inspiriert, das jedoch nur Dialoge im Textmodus anzeigt.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Το kdialog σας επιτρέπει να εμφανίζετε πλαίσια διαλόγου από σενάρια φλοιού. Η σύνταξη έχει επηρεαστεί πολύ από την εντολή "dialog" (η οποία εμφανίζει κείμενο και διαλόγους).</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">kdialog allows you to display dialogue boxes from shell scripts. The syntax is very much inspired from the "dialog" command (which shows text mode dialogues).</p>
    <p xml:lang="eo">kdialog permesas al vi montri dialogkestojn el ŝelskriptoj. La sintakso estas pleje inspirita de la komando "dialog" (kiu montras tekstreĝimajn dialogujojn).</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">KDialog le permite mostrar cuadros de diálogo desde los scripts del intérprete de órdenes. Su sintaxis está muy inspirada en la orden «dialog» (que muestra diálogos en modo de texto).</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">kdialog võimaldab shelliskriptide abil kuvada dialoogikaste. Süntaks on põhiliselt võtnud eeskuju käsust "dialog" (mis kuvab tekstirežiimis dialooge).</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">kdialog-ek «shell script»etatik elkarrizketa-koadroak bistaratzen uzten dizu. Sintaxia «dialog» komandoaren antzerakoa egin da (testu moduan elkarrizketak erakusten dituena).</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">KDialogilla voi näyttää komentotulkkiskriptistä kyselyikkunoita. Syntaksi on saanut vaikutteita dialog-komennosta (joka näyttää tekstitilan kyselyikkunoita).</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">KDialog vous permet d'afficher des boîtes de dialogue depuis des scripts shell. Sa syntaxe s'inspire de celle de la commande « dialog » (qui affiche des boîtes de dialogue en mode texte).</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">kdialog permítelle mostrar cadros de diálogo a partir de scripts de intérprete de ordes. A sintaxe está inspirada en gran medida na orde «dialog» (que mostra diálogos en modo texto).</p>
    <p xml:lang="hi">के-डायलॉग आपको शेल स्क्रिप्टों से संवाद बक्से प्रदर्शित करने में मदद करता है। इसका सिंटैक्स काफी कुछ "डायलॉग" कमांड से प्रेरित है (जो पाठ मोड संवाद दिखाता है)।</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">A kdialog lehetővé teszi párbeszédablakok megjelenítését parancsfájlokból. A szintaxisára nagy hatással volt a „dialog” parancs (amely szöveges párbeszédablakokat jelenít meg).</p>
    <p xml:lang="ia">kdialog te permitte monstrar quadros de dialogo ex scripts de shell. Le synthaxe es multe inspirate al commando  "dialog"  (que monstra dialogos de modo texto).</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">kdialog memungkinkan kamu untuk mendisplaikan kotak dialog dari skrip shell. Sintaksnya sangat terinspirasi dari perintah "dialog" (yang menampilkan dialog mode teks).</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">kdialog ti permette di visualizzare delle finestre di dialogo da script di shell. La sintassi prende decisamente ispirazione dal comando «dialog» (che mostra finestre in modalità testuale).</p>
    <p xml:lang="ka">kdialog საშუალებას გაძლევთ, გრაფიკული ფანჯრები გარსის სკრიპტებიდან გამოიძახოთ. სინტაქსი ძალიან წააგავს "dialog" ბრძანებისას (რომელიც იგივეს ტექსტურ რეჟიმში აკეთებს).</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">KDialog를 사용하여 셸 스크립트에서 대화 상자를 표시할 수 있습니다. 텍스트 모드 대화 상자를 표시하는 "dialog" 명령의 문법에서 많은 영향을 받았습니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">kdialog biedt u dialoogvensters te tonen uit shell-scripts. De syntaxis is zeer geïnspireerd op het commando "dialog" (die dialogen toont in tekstmodus).</p>
    <p xml:lang="nn">KDialog lèt deg visa dialogvindauge frå kommandolinjeskript. Syntaksen er sterkt inspirert av «dialog»-kommandoen (som viser tekstbaserte dialogvindauge).</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">kdialog umożliwia wyświetlanie okien dialogowych ze skryptów powłoki. Składnia naśladuje polecenie "dialog" (które pokazuje tekstowe okna dialogowe).</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O KDialog permite-lhe mostrar janelas interactivas a partir de programas na consola. A sintaxe é muito semelhante à do "dialog" (o qual mostra janelas em modo de texto).</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">O KDialog permite-lhe mostrar caixas de diálogo a partir de scripts do shell. A sintaxe é muito semelhante à do comando "dialog" (que mostra caixa de diálogos em modo de texto).</p>
    <p xml:lang="ro">kdialog permite afișarea casetelor de dialog din scripturi de consolă. Sintaxa e inspirată din comanda „dialog” (care arată dialoguri în regim textual).</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">KDialog служит для показа диалоговых окон из сценариев оболочки. Синтаксис основан на синтаксисе программы «dialog», предназначенной для показа диалоговых окон в текстовом режиме.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">kdialog vám umožní zobraziť dialógové okná zo shellových skriptov. Syntax je inšpirovaná príkazom "dialog" (ktorý zobrazí textové dialógy)</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">kdialog omogoča prikazovanje pogovornih oken iz shell skripta. Skladnja je navdihnjena iz ukaza "dialog" (ki prikazuje besedilni načindialogov).</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Kdialog låter dig visa dialogrutor från skalskript. Syntaxen är i stor utsträckning inspirerad av kommandot "dialog" (som visar dialogrutor i textläge).</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">kdialog, kabuk betiklerinden iletişim kutuları görüntülemenize izin verir. Sözdizim, büyük ölçüde "dialog" komutundan (metin kipi iletişim kutuları gösterir) esinlenmiştir.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">За допомогою kdialog можна відкривати діалогові вікна зі скриптів командної оболонки. Синтаксис команд є дуже схожим на синтаксис команд програми «dialog» (яка показу діалогові вікна у текстовому режимі).</p>
    <p xml:lang="vi">kdialog cho phép bạn hiển thị các hộp thoại từ các kịch bản hệ vỏ. Cú pháp của nó gần với lệnh "dialog" (hiển thị hộp thoại ở chế độ chữ).</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxkdialog allows you to display dialog boxes from shell scripts. The syntax is very much inspired from the "dialog" command (which shows text mode dialogs).xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">kdialog 允许您从 Shell 脚本中显示一个对话框。语法深受 dialog 命令影响 (显示文本模式的对话框)。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-TW">kdialog 讓你能使用 Shell 指令稿顯示對話框。語法不少啟發自「dialog」（顯示文字模式的對話框）指令。</p>
  </description>
  <icon type="stock">dialog-question</icon>
  <url type="homepage">https://www.kde.org</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=kdialog</url>
  <url type="help">https://techbase.kde.org/Development/Tutorials/Shell_Scripting_with_KDE_Dialogs</url>
  <url type="donation">https://www.kde.org/community/donations/?app=kdialog&amp;source=appdata</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/kdialog/kdialog.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>kdialog</binary>
  </provides>
  <categories>
    <category>Utility</category>
  </categories>
  <releases>
    <release version="22.12.2" date="2023-02-02"/>
    <release version="22.12.1" date="2023-01-05"/>
    <release version="22.12.0" date="2022-12-08"/>
    <release version="22.08.3" date="2022-11-03"/>
  </releases>
</component>
